<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<myapps>

<entry>Deezer Scope</entry>
<entry xml:lang="it">Deezer Scope</entry>
<entry xml:lang="nl">Deezer Scope</entry>

<entry>Unofficial app to discover the Deezer database</entry>
<entry xml:lang="it">App non ufficiale per esplorare il database di Deezer</entry>
<entry xml:lang="nl">Officieuze app om de Deezer database te ontdekken</entry>

<entry>Discover the wide range of music in the Deezer database. You can listen to previews and view the details of the wide collection of Deezer songs.
Surfacing mode allows to discover new artists per genre.

Search mode searches for tracks, artists and albums.
Advanced searches can also be performed with:
'artist: <artist name>'
'album: <album name>'
'track: <track name>'
'label: <lable name>'
'dur_min: <minimum duration in sec>'
'dur_max: <maximum duration in sec>'
'bpm_min <minimum bpm>'
'bpm_max <maximum bpm>'

The sorting can be set in the settings.

Setting up an account, getting more personalized results and translations will be implemented in the near future.

Translators:
Emanuele Antonio Faraone (it)

Feel free to contact me for translations.

!!This app is in no way affiliated with www.deezer.com.!!</entry>
<entry xml:lang="nl">Ontdek het ruime aanbod muziek in de Deezer databank. Je kan info bezien en previews beluisteren van de weide collectie muziek op Deezer.
In Surfacing modus kan je nieuwe artisten ontdekken per genre.

In zoek modus kan je naar nummers, artisten en albums zoken.
Er zijn ook geavenceerde zoektermen:
'artist: <naam>'
'album: <naam>'
'track: <naam>'
'label: <naam>'
'dur_min: <minimum aantal seconden>'
'dur_max: <maximum aantal seconden>'
'bpm_min <min bpm>'
'bpm_max <max bpm>'

Het sorteren van de resultaten kan worden ingesteld in de scope instellingen.
Uw Account, gepersonaliseerde resultaten en vertalingen zullen later nog volgen..

Vertalers:
Emanuele Antonio Faraone (it)

Laat gerust iets weten als je wilt helpen vertalen.

!!Deze applicatie is op geen enkele manier verbonden aan www.deezer.com.!!</entry>

<entry>deezer, music, stream, discover, scope</entry>
<entry xml:lang="it">Deezer, musica, stream, esplora, scope</entry>
<entry xml:lang="nl">Deezer, muziek, stream, ontdek, scope</entry>
</myapps>